[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had no choice but to stay but will take this as far as we can .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In an apparently unrelated incidents , some eleven Iraqis were killed by snipers on Tuesday , including a group of police trainees in a bus near Hilla and two police in Kirkuk .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"Iraqis\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In short , China has the American economy by the throat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"China\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"One resident of New Orleans said escaping from the storm was \" hell \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"resident\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"And he earned 112 points in 1971 - 1972 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"earned\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Sufaat was arrested in December 2001 upon his return to Malaysia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I told Paul that you called him yesterday so abruptly because you did n't want to waste his time while you got tests done for arthritis .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"All you want is for \" them \" to get on with it - and to leave you alone ..\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"All\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"you speak the language and will have more fun .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"speak\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I like shrimp , fried , grilled , or steamed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"like\", does the participant \"shrimp\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know that we address audit rights in the LLC agreement so this may not matter anyway if this is a right they already have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"address\", does the participant \"rights\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"\" We applaud China 's space achievements , \" NASA spokesman Allard Beutel said Tuesday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Beutel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said Mr Dar , 33 , was arrested in Indian - administered Kashmir and belonged to the outlawed Lashkar - e - Toiba militant group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Dar\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"India 's Andaman and Nicobar Islands comprise more than 500 islands lying 1,000 kilometers east of Sri Lanka in the Bay of Bengal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"comprise\", does the participant \"Islands\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"complete\", does the participant \"job\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The plants provide shade and root strength for bank stability .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"plants\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Last June , an international initiative led by Japan to persuade the LTTE to come back to the negotiating table failed despite an aid package offer of US$ 4.5 billion .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"failed\", does the participant \"initiative\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Husbands marry mothers and teen daughters at the same time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"marry\", does the participant \"Husbands\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They both went to jail and a new manager was put in charge of the apartments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"went\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"It has two parts , both of which are timed for 90 seconds each and the differential between the resulting two scores determines the likelihood of having a learning disability or attention deficit disorder .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"timed\", does the participant \"both\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" I hope that industry , if put to the test , can do better [ than the government ] , but I do not expect it , \" Griffin added .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"expect\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the participant \"eggs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I thought that I had gained my cockatiel 's trust , but now he 's not coming to me when I open his cage .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"open\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You have two adjustment screws for up and down and right to left positions .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Bush did no such thing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"Bush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Iran in particular feared that Qanooni would loose and then be politically isolated from the mainstream .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"feared\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The biggest LTTE maritime disaster was reported in the now - defunct Asiaweek in 2001 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reported\", does the participant \"disaster\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"EVERYTHING IN HERE SEEMS TO AMAZE ME !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"SEEMS\", does the participant \"EVERYTHING\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This BuzzMachine post argues that Google 's rush toward ubiquity might backfire -- which we 've all heard before , but it 's particularly well - put in this post .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"backfire\", does the participant \"rush\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vaulted\", does the participant \"mission\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I called the front desk and got no answer .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"desk\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He showed me the car I was interested in and we took a test drive .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"showed\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"push\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"There is a painting on my wall in the Oval -- first of all , I do n't know .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"painting\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Even Zawahiri 's attorney in 1999 said that Bin Laden and Zawahiri were likely to resort to the biological and chemical agents they possessed given the extradition pressure senior Al Qaeda leaders faced .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"attorney\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Fortier\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Prices for electricity jumped from an average of $ 249 a megawatt to $ 700 a megawatt within three days , ISO records show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jumped\", does the participant \"Prices\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"And they deliver !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deliver\", does the participant \"they\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bisconti wanted over $ 300 to fix my laptop and these guys fixed it for $ 90 !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fixed\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I called her grandmother and explained things to her .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"called\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The investors put big bucks into the building but are clueless about what makes a good dining or bar experience .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"put\", does the participant \"investors\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" There is always the possibility they could jam us up , make us look like we are not numero uno , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jam\", does the participant \"us\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I MAKE MONEY NOT DEAL WITH BROKERS \" Wow , can you believe in today s tough times this dealership would be looking for any way to move vehicles .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"MAKE\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"This means that I could be away from the office for several days and miss a message entirely , because it would have expired and disappeared by the time I returned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"miss\", does the participant \"message\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"For weeks , reporters scoured Alabama in search of pilots or anyone who might have remembered seeing Mr. Bush at the time he was serving in the National Guard there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scoured\", does the participant \"Alabama\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We were told by a detective and asked to check our credit for anything unusual .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Both India and Afghanistan deny the claim .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"deny\", does the participant \"India\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"A sender purporting to be islamist sent cyanide in both early 2002 and early 2003 in New Zealand and ingredients of nerve gas in Belgium in 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"cyanide\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"sorry , i left lou off of the message .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"We love Little Farmer\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"Farmer\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I propose we have a conference call with Bob Fagan on Fri July 20 at 1:00 pm Calgary time to discuss any areas of concern / confusion you may have .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"propose\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I remain devoted full - time to the advancement of Firefox , the Mozilla platform and web browsing in general .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I started with 21 email addresses .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Mark Elliott tells me that you drafted some trader guidelines ( physical and financial ) for the London traders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"drafted\", does the participant \"guidelines\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Well , they have a variety of sports that they play like basketball , soccer , etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"variety\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They provide an emotional infrastructure for atrocities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"infrastructure\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He showed me the car I was interested in and we took a test drive .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"showed\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said Mr Dar , 33 , was arrested in Indian - administered Kashmir and belonged to the outlawed Lashkar - e - Toiba militant group .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Dar\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Hiller asked Bush to name the leaders of Chechnya , Taiwan , India and Pakistan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"Hiller\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a cat named GummiBear , so no , R2D2 is not a stupid name .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I melt brass and cast it http://www.mikegigi.com/castgobl.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"melt\", does the participant \"brass\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"the guy came on time and did n't take any breaks , he went straight to work and finished the job efficiently and promptly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finished\", does the participant \"job\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I spoke with Jeff Hodge yesterday regarding the additional language from Peoples regarding Audit Rights .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spoke\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Midas has the most high tech equipment in town & I guarantee you if they told you it was electrical then in deed it s electrical !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"Midas\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I left you a voice mail on Friday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"left\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The owners of Bowtie manged to add something new while preserving what was already there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manged\", does the participant \"owners\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"You take a boat across the river , then spend a day biking , eating at a local restaurant , buying souvenirs and doing other things that are geared towards tourists .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buying\", does the participant \"souvenirs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I ordered 1000 postcards , we normally order 5000 or more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"order\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The investors put big bucks into the building but are clueless about what makes a good dining or bar experience .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"put\", does the participant \"investors\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought the UK was completely devoid of good NYC style pizza .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The classes cover all age and skill ranges , with BALLROOM , LATIN , SEQUENCE , STREET , DISCO , LINE DANCING , BALLET , TAP & JAZZ .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cover\", does the participant \"ranges\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love the location and the apartment !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"location\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In Texas , BP shut its 460,000 barrels per day refinery and Marathon shut its 72,000 bpd plant .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"shut\", does the participant \"BP\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( News assistant Bobby Bender recalls the letter containing the items to have been addressed to The Sun . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recalls\", does the participant \"letter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The 99 - tonne cache of AK47s was to have been secretly flown out from a US base in Bosnia .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"was\", does the participant \"cache\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yet people seem willing -- even eager -- to accommodate mountain lions , despite the risks .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accommodate\", does the participant \"lions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"They interviewed me , gave me tests in the software I included on my resume , and placed me in a position that I kept for several years .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"interviewed\", does the participant \"me\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They did that with no problem .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"They want to use LTS to tie into NASA 's vision for Space Exploration , and seem pleased that the White House is moving in that direction .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"want\", does the participant \"They\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The problem with this argument is that Bush lacked the experience necessary to be president when he ran in 2000 , so this sort of cheap shot just hoists him by his own petard .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My cat had a seizure yesterday and was ill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed the animations and wanted to share them with my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"share\", does the participant \"them\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Disney cruises offer 24 - hour room services , and the crews are ready to serve you the way you like .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"offer\", does the participant \"cruises\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"'' President Musharraf promised to help us and cooperate with us on curbing terrorist activity by the Taliban , '' says Karzai .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"curbing\", does the participant \"activity\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He showed me the car I was interested in and we took a test drive .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"showed\", does the participant \"car\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The thing to do is to bring the right clothing with you , clothes so you can layer up if it is cold and take off layers when it warms up .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"layer\", does the participant \"you\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had my wedding luncheon at this BJ s restaurant , and it was one of the best choices that I made .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"luncheon\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Al - Sharq al - Awsat reports that a key eyewitness in the trial of Saddam Hussein for a 1982 massacre at Dujail has died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"eyewitness\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I visited their huge Chicago lighting showroom and all I have to say is WOW !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"visited\", does the participant \"showroom\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The only neurological sign that he shows is that he barely drags his toes and sometimes has trouble with his right lead .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"sign\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Jewish marriage living to the right of George 's house said that he is an arrogant person who does never return a greeting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"marriage\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The Ten Degree Channel divides the Andamans , which are the larger and more heavily populated northern islands , from the 20 or so Nicobar Islands in the south .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"divides\", does the participant \"Channel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This means that messages initiated at Corp and intended for the entire Enron organization will not reach any business units outside the Corp domain .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"means\", does the participant \"This\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"A sender purporting to be islamist sent cyanide in both early 2002 and early 2003 in New Zealand and ingredients of nerve gas in Belgium in 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"cyanide\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"An analysis of 65 bird species in the United Kingdom shows about one - third are laying their eggs four to seven days earlier than they did 25 years ago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"laying\", does the participant \"eggs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"This means that I could be away from the office for several days and miss a message entirely , because it would have expired and disappeared by the time I returned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"miss\", does the participant \"message\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Two vaunted economists - one a Nobel Prize winner and the other a nationally renowned budget expert - have analyzed the data at hand and put a price tag on the Iraq occupation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"analyzed\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"For weeks , reporters scoured Alabama in search of pilots or anyone who might have remembered seeing Mr. Bush at the time he was serving in the National Guard there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"scoured\", does the participant \"Alabama\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have to mention that i recently separated the father into another cage close to the ' nest cage ' because he and the mother were fighting .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"fighting\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Police in the Indian capital Delhi say they have arrested the suspected co-ordinator and financier of last month 's deadly bomb blasts in the city .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"co-ordinator\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the same time McCartney was going out with Heather Mills , he used Linda 's death for promotional ends , due to his waning popularity .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"That indicates that they thrive in different water chemistries .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicates\", does the participant \"That\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Many point to the trillion spore concentration as extraordinary .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"point\", does the participant \"Many\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have 4 Golden Wonder Killifish .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"But there are strong hints in the country that a new Indo - Sri Lanka defense deal could be in the making .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"hints\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You informed me that you would discuss this with your attorney .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"informed\", does the participant \"You\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Within seven days , I started getting money in the mail !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I promise you that if you follow the directions exactly that you will start making more money than you thought possible by doing something so easy !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"follow\", does the participant \"directions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I purchased a 2 - year old certified pre-owned BMW from this dealership .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Jim Lobe has more on the political implications of the Fallujah assault , both in Iraq and in Washington .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"more\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Iran in particular feared that Qanooni would loose and then be politically isolated from the mainstream .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"feared\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"cats react to the treatment they receive , they are not toys .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"react\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"To the north in Lebanon , there is serious debate within Hezbollah about entering the Lebanese political process in light of Syria 's promised withdrawal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"entering\", does the participant \"process\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Iran is encircled by Afghanistan , by the Gulf States , Iraq and the Moslem republics of the former Soviet Union .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"encircled\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yes , they all have secret locator chips , just like gps\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"chips\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the participant \"reports\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" ( China ) could be the second country to do that , \" Pike said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Pike\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Prices for electricity jumped from an average of $ 249 a megawatt to $ 700 a megawatt within three days , ISO records show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"jumped\", does the participant \"Prices\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another connection to Philippine terror and weapons smuggling - dating from the 1980s - is alleged in the book Disposable Patriot , by Jack Terrell .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"alleged\", does the participant \"connection\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"The Leads who are responsible for Associates are as follows :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"Leads\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You take a boat across the river , then spend a day biking , eating at a local restaurant , buying souvenirs and doing other things that are geared towards tourists .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"buying\", does the participant \"souvenirs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I thought the UK was completely devoid of good NYC style pizza .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In the meantime , we extend our best wishes for a safe and happy holiday season .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"extend\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"US - trained Malaysian biochemist Yazid Sufaat met with 9/11 plotters and two hijackers in January 2000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"met\", does the participant \"Sufaat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In response to the rockets , Israel resumed its policy of targeting militant leaders in air strikes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"resumed\", does the participant \"Israel\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"As concerned citizens we affirm the liberty of adults of the same gender to love and marry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"affirm\", does the participant \"we\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We order take out from here all the time and we are never disappointed .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"order\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Any of the tip - top places have great ice - cream , get them to mix it up .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cream\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" Their screams changed , \" Dr. Fortier said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Fortier\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Saddam killed every month more people than all those who died from suicide murders since the Coalition occupation of Iraq .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"those\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My nails looked great for the better part of 2 weeks !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"looked\", does the participant \"nails\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I have a Nacho Libre question .?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"cats react to the treatment they receive , they are not toys .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"react\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Police\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sheriff 's deputies in Louisiana made a third arrest Wednesday in the ongoing investigation of a case involving allegations of sexual abuse of children and animals at a Ponchatoula , La. , church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"arrest\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i think they could get their asses kicked by cats .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" There 's no tracking mechanism in place \" ?!?!?\"\nQuestion: In the event \"'s\", does the participant \"mechanism\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I ended up paying much more .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paying\", does the participant \"more\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I thought it would pass until he started to vomit blood and would nt drink any water .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i have a 1 and a half year old male neutered cat and a new 2 month old spayed female kitten .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In a timid voice , he says : \" If an airplane carrying Winston Peters was blown up by a bomb , THAT would be a tragedy \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"carrying\", does the participant \"Peters\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"We were told by a detective and asked to check our credit for anything unusual .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She said a shower would be grand .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"She\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"In a highly significant move Afghan Pashtun tribes along the Pakistan border warned the Taliban in Quetta and Chaman that if they try and disrupt the elections , they would be resisted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"disrupt\", does the participant \"elections\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We need to change the lock and place posted signs at the gate .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"place\", does the participant \"signs\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"jill allen finishes her cpa today and she and her friends are going to party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"finishes\", does the participant \"allen\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is rumored that North Korea has at least a couple nuclear weapons .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"rumored\", does the participant \"It\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I knew a cat that died in its sleep aged 21 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"cat\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"TEXAS ROADHOUSE HAS VERY GOOD MEALS , THAT THE MEAT COMES RIGHT OFF THE BONES .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"HAS\", does the participant \"MEALS\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"involving\", does the participant \"children\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are special regions uniquely and imposingly designed for the children .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"are\", does the participant \"regions\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I love it for discounted beauty items and household appliances .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"it\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I believe we are to some extent already protected with \" Enron \" proceeded with anything , but EnronOnline ( TM ) , etc. just affords us more protection .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believe\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The problem with this argument is that Bush lacked the experience necessary to be president when he ran in 2000 , so this sort of cheap shot just hoists him by his own petard .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"he\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Seth provides deep tissue massage which has significantly reduced the pain in my neck and shoulders and added flexibility and movement back to the area .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"Seth\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"My last rabbit did that a few times , and he was fine ...\"\nQuestion: In the event \"did\", does the participant \"that\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The bear dwarfed the 6 - foot - 1 Mr. Parenteau , knocking him to the ground , he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dwarfed\", does the participant \"Parenteau\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I graduate in the spring , and so we 'd like to go between then and winter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"graduate\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We refer to licensed Fuel Cell Energy equipment .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"refer\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I have 4 Golden Wonder Killifish .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Within seven days , I started getting money in the mail !!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"\" The governor believes it was the defining moment , when what was a mounting problem turned into an instant crisis , \" Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"believes\", does the participant \"governor\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"animals\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"NASA has some PR hurdles to overcome in the future .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"hurdles\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said the main aim of the subpoenas will be to determine whether collusion occurred to \" fix \" prices , which would violate federal trade laws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"violate\", does the participant \"laws\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Musk , which is scraped from their genitals once a day for as long as they can surv ive , makes the scent of perfume last a bit longer after each application .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"makes\", does the participant \"Musk\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I purchased a 2 - year old certified pre-owned BMW from this dealership .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"purchased\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Many point to the trillion spore concentration as extraordinary .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"point\", does the participant \"Many\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"daughter\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"Attached is PG&E 's Gas Accord II ( GA II ) Settlement Proposal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"Proposal\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Iran in particular feared that Qanooni would loose and then be politically isolated from the mainstream .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"feared\", does the participant \"Iran\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"In Baghdad Kadhim Talal Husain , assistant dean at the School of Education at Mustansiriyah University , was assassinated with his driver in the Salikh district .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"Husain\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"cats react to the treatment they receive , they are not toys .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"react\", does the participant \"cats\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"I use propane with a blower and a burner I built http://www.mikegigi.com/meltmetl.htm and http://www.mikegigi.com/firehole.htm\"\nQuestion: In the event \"built\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sheriff 's deputies in Louisiana made a third arrest Wednesday in the ongoing investigation of a case involving allegations of sexual abuse of children and animals at a Ponchatoula , La. , church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"deputies\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"The clerics demanded talks with local US commanders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"demanded\", does the participant \"talks\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I took some photos of my model girlfriend with my Nikon D7000 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Wiki Media Foundation , the group behind the Wikipedia online encyclopedia project , said Friday that search giant Google has volunteered to host some of its content on company servers .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Foundation\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"JUNO AND OPEN I LOVE YOU GUYS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"LOVE\", does the participant \"YOU\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"These links present the many viewpoints that existed and still exist about the disaster called Chernobyl :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"present\", does the participant \"links\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I love this place lots of people to talk to and school is across the street !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"place\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"He explained that interrogations and other evidence revealed that Al Qaeda wanted to strike the US with a nonconventional weapon , most notably anthrax .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"strike\", does the participant \"US\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Family owned and operated makes sure the atmosphere is relaxed and the food home - cooked with style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cooked\", does the participant \"food\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"All you want is for \" them \" to get on with it - and to leave you alone ..\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"All\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We go to Japaneiro 's all the time and we have NEVER been disappointed !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"go\", does the participant \"We\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Kapor used to be a teacher of Transcendental Meditation of Maharishi Mahesh Yogi .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"used\", does the participant \"Kapor\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Pakistani press reported that she was nabbed in Karachi after being spotted at the airport in late March or early April 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"nabbed\", does the participant \"she\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"I think this place is probably really great especially judging by the reviews on here .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At 3:15 am on night # 2 , the fire alarm and strobe light activated in my room .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"activated\", does the participant \"alarm\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"oh god is there an agenda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"agenda\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The owners of Bowtie manged to add something new while preserving what was already there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manged\", does the participant \"owners\" act with volition?\nAnswer: Yes\nSentence: \"Chahine said her immediate family spent about $ 20,000 to return to Detroit via Syria and Jordan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spent\", does the participant \"$\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Several candidates were assassinated and targeted these last two weeks , others have been forced under threats to withdraw and to follow the example of the Islamic party .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"candidates\" act with volition?\nAnswer: No\nSentence: \"i agree , Hmmmmmm .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"agree\", does the participant \"i\" act with volition?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]